Hello Gas, welcome to the video stock
market friends, ICC Prudential Life
Insurance Company Limited has
presented its June quarter financial results,
both consolidated and standardized results have been released, we will
access them in today's video,
friends, let's start the video, first we will look at the
consolidated results, the
numbers are given in the left, so here on the
screen, if you talk about its income, the
company's income was Rs
23541 crore, in the last quarter it was Rs 11499
crore, in Arjun 22 quarter
if you look here, there was a loss of Rs 1461 crore
in income, which can be seen here, the
income of cotton quarter air is also seeing very
strong growth, which
can be seen here, gas here and but
see here gas, there was a
loss in income, the income was in negative, the
biggest region of which is gas net
premium income, which can be seen, sorry
gas, here the income from investment means
investment, which this company earns income from, which is  There was a
loss of 8670 kg, its
income was seen in negative here
because a very strong rise is being seen in the income of the cotton quarter, the
expense is
23340 crores, in the previous quarter it was
10000640 crores and in the June 22 quarter it is
seen in negative, in
which the
expense is also increased in the quarter, order and on air, after this the
operating profit is 200 crores, here the
operating profit is 859 crores in the previous quarter,
Arjun is
224 crores, a
lot of
results are being seen in the quarter, the net
profit of the company which has come out,
if seen, here it is 2006
crores, in the previous quarter it was 200.35
crores, in the June 22 quarter there
is a need profit of 156 crores, Quadran is also having a draw
but this is seeing a rise in the along near,
which you can see here,
if it has come out with a positive sign  There has been a
rise in the profit of the company,
this time a little growth is being seen in the profit of the company,
if we talk about net earnings here,
which is 1.43 percent in the quarter
and there was a rise in earnings,
overall, which dated average
result was presented here, then if we look at its
standard earnings results, the number was
23541 crore, in the last quarter it was
11499.8 crore, in the Arjun 22 quarter there was an
income of 1461 crore in negative
because in the quarter they are
seeing a rise in both earnings and earnings,
if we look at the expenses of the company this time, then the expenses here which are
23340 crore in the last quantum of 10000 640
crore, in the Arjun 22 quarter there was an
expense of 1856 crore in negative
because it is a cotton coat, the expenses of Aaron also
increased, operating profit has declined here
Operating profit is Rs 200.6 crore, Rs 859 crore in the last quarter and Rs 3004.9 crore in the June 22 quarter. A
lot of profit is being seen in the modern quarter air,
but the company has received funds
here for future appropriations,
which is sorry, the
funds have been debited here, which is Rs 1078 crore,
its
profit has fallen even more,
after that the net profit which has been calculated here,
if you see it here, its
profit is Rs 2006.9 crore,
in the last quarter it is Rs 234.8 crore, in the June 22
quarter there is a net profit of Rs 1505 crore, there is a
profit in the cotton quarter and there is a growth in the on-going, the
company has
calculated the profit, which if seen this time, the
profit here is
Rs 1.4 crore, there is a profit in cotton, this is the
growth in the range air, so overall the average
result has been calculated here because cotton cotton  There is a
decline in profits, so now we just
print the video and
I get it in the comment box.